{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":6900,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Back to Basics ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_265","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_265","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106","Image_265"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_284","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_285","roles":{}},{"id":"si33083","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1109","roles":{}},{"id":"si32980","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_964","title":"1.  For applications or accounts that require passwords, creating a new strong password should include:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32991","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1097","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32995","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1098","title":"Difficult dictionary words ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32991_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_522","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Difficult dictionary words\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1099","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33006","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1100","title":"Common phrases like “Passwords 12345678’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33002_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"523","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Common phrases like “Passwords 12345678’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1101","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33017","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1102","title":"Things known to you like your birthdate, address or phone number ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33013_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"526","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Having a key card and a password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33024","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1103","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33028","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1104","title":"Numbers, symbols, upper and lowercase letters ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33024_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"528","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Numbers, symbols, upper and lowercase letters\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33280","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33280_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1108","roles":{}},{"id":"si33105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_211","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_212","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_213","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_214","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33175","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33187","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33199","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33211","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33223","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33235","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33247","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33259","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33272q0","for":"Slide33272q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33047","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1105","title":"Correct - Answer:D  Even difficult dictionary words, unless part of a random phrase, can be discovered with a dictionary attack. Common phrases are far too easy to guess or crack with ‘brute force’. Things known to you could be gotten from a previous breach of your information. A mixture of numbers, symbols, upper and lowercase words in a phrase would be the most difficult to guess.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33059","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1106","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  Even difficult dictionary words, unless part of a random phrase, can be discovered with a dictionary attack. Common phrases are far too easy to guess or crack with ‘brute force’. Things known to you could be gotten from a previous breach of your information. A mixture of numbers, symbols, upper and lowercase words in a phrase would be the most difficult to guess.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33071","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1107","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33272","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_284","Image_285","si32980","si32995","si33006","si33017","si33028","si33284","si33105","si33123","si33145","si33163","si33175","si33187","si33199","si33211","si33223","si33235","si33247","si33259","si33071"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33272"},"question":{"interactionId":"32954","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  For applications or accounts that require passwords, creating a new strong password should include:\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_278","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_279","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_279","roles":{}},{"id":"si32048","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1070","roles":{}},{"id":"si31945","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_961","title":"2. What is the most important thing you can do when adding something new to your technology environment, whether it’s a social media account, new app, IoT device, Wi-Fi upgrade, or other?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31956","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1058","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1059","title":"Read the terms and change the default password ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31956_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_510","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Read the terms and change the default password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si31967","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1060","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31971","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1061","title":"Use a separate network from the one used for confidential information (banking, etc.)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31967_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_511","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a separate network from the one used for confidential information (banking, etc.) \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1062","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1063","title":"Ensure you set strong security settings (no sharing) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31978_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"507_512","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure you set strong security settings (no sharing)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1064","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1065","title":"Ensure you have the newest version with relevant patches already installed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"509_513","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure you have the newest version with relevant patches already installed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1069","roles":{}},{"id":"si32070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_199","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_200","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_201","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_202","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32152","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32164","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32200","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32212","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32237q1","for":"Slide32237q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1066","title":"Correct - Answer:   A  All of the above are great measures to secure your new technology or accounts however, none of them will protect you if someone knows the default password or if you have agreed to certain terms. Once you check ‘I agree’, they have full control over what is allowed in the agreement (ex: sharing personal information and habits, all of your contacts, your network address, etc.). It is never convenient but take the time to read your terms before agreeing.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32024","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1067","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  All of the above are great measures to secure your new technology or accounts however, none of them will protect you if someone knows the default password or if you have agreed to certain terms. Once you check ‘I agree’, they have full control over what is allowed in the agreement (ex: sharing personal information and habits, all of your contacts, your network address, etc.). It is never convenient but take the time to read your terms before agreeing.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32036","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1068","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32237","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_278","Image_279","si31945","si31960","si31971","si31982","si31993","si32070","si32088","si32110","si32128","si32140","si32152","si32164","si32176","si32188","si32200","si32212","si32224","si32036"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32237"},"question":{"interactionId":"31919","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What is the most important thing you can do when adding something new to your technology environment, whether it’s a social media account, new app, IoT device, Wi-Fi upgrade, or other?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_280","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_280","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_281","roles":{}},{"id":"si32393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1083","roles":{}},{"id":"si32290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_962","title":"3.  With all of the awareness information, training, initiatives and internal campaigns, people are finally getting wise to phishing. It is not as effective or prevalent as it used to be.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1071","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32305","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1072","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32301_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_514","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1073","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1074","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_515","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si32387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1082","roles":{}},{"id":"si32415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_203","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_204","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_205","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_206","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32582q2","for":"Slide32582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1079","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Even with all of our efforts, phishing is still extremely effective. The APWG’s Phishing Activity Trends Report shows phishing sites (where bad links take you) increased to nearly 166,000 with steady increases each quarter. One disturbing fact, 75% of all phishing sites now use SSL protection.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1080","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Even with all of our efforts, phishing is still extremely effective.The APWG’s Phishing Activity Trends Report shows phishing sites (where bad links take you) increased to nearly 166,000 with steady increases each quarter. One disturbing fact, 75% of all phishing sites now use SSL protection.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1081","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_280","Image_281","si32290","si32305","si32316","si32415","si32433","si32455","si32473","si32485","si32497","si32509","si32521","si32533","si32545","si32557","si32569","si32381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32582"},"question":{"interactionId":"32264","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  With all of the awareness information, training, initiatives and internal campaigns, people are finally getting wise to phishing. It is not as effective or prevalent as it used to be.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_282","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_283","roles":{}},{"id":"si32738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1096","roles":{}},{"id":"si32635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_963","title":"4. Internet connected (IoT) devices are everywhere (e.g.: home assistants, vacuums, refrigerators, washers/dryers, thermostats, smart locks,  doorbells, lights, cameras, etc.). What are some of the security concerns?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1084","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1085","title":"Devices from smaller companies are not properly equipped or tested for security ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_518","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Devices from smaller companies are not properly equipped or tested for security\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1086","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1087","title":"Manufacturers do not inform customers to change default passwords or settings ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_519","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Manufacturers do not inform customers to change default passwords or settings\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32668","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1088","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32672","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1089","title":"Vulnerability to network infection or extraction of data and personal information  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32668_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"507_520","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Vulnerability to network infection or extraction of data and personal information \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32679","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1090","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32683","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1091","title":"Untrusted communications to and from your network without encryption ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32679_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"509_521","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Untrusted communications to and from your network without encryption\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33299","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33295_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si32732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1095","roles":{}},{"id":"si32760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_207","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_208","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32800","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_209","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32818","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_210","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32890","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32927q3","for":"Slide32927q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32702","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1092","title":"Correct - Answer:  E All of these plus many more concerns are associated with IoT devices. It is recommended to engage a second network (many home routers have this feature) to separate the network used for confidential information from the one used for IoT devices. Always change default passwords and use the most secure settings that will still allow functionality. Take a minute to consider the benefit -vs- the risk of loss of data and privacy before connecting any device.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1093","title":"Incorrect - Answer: E All of these plus many more concerns are associated with IoT devices. It is recommended to engage a second network (many home routers have this feature) to separate the network used for confidential information from the one used for IoT devices. Always change default passwords and use the most secure settings that will still allow functionality. Take a minute to consider the benefit -vs- the risk of loss of data and privacy before connecting any device.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1094","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32927","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_282","Image_283","si32635","si32650","si32661","si32672","si32683","si33299","si32760","si32778","si32800","si32818","si32830","si32842","si32854","si32866","si32878","si32890","si32902","si32914","si32726"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32927"},"question":{"interactionId":"32609","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. Internet connected (IoT) devices are everywhere (e.g.: home assistants, vacuums, refrigerators, washers/dryers, thermostats, smart locks,  doorbells, lights, cameras, etc.). What are some of the security concerns?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_286","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_287","roles":{}},{"id":"si33473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1124","roles":{}},{"id":"si33359","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_965","title":"5.  Another way for criminals to find your personal information (personal data, preferences, etc.) is from extracting it from your browser.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33370","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1110","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1111","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33370_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_529","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1112","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1113","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33381_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_530","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33467","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1123","roles":{}},{"id":"si33495","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_215","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_216","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33535","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_217","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33553","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_218","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33625","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33662q4","for":"Slide33662q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33437","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1120","title":"Correct - Answer:  A Your browser can show many pieces of information about you: your IP address, computer settings, cookies and saved authentication information (to name a few). All of the pieces can be put together to create a profile with information such as: websites you have visited, accounts you hold, your preferences and habits. Consider using two different browsers - one for confidential browsing (banking, business, etc.) and one for miscellaneous browsing.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1121","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A Your browser can show many pieces of information about you: your IP address, computer settings, cookies and saved authentication information (to name a few). All of the pieces can be put together to create a profile with information such as: websites you have visited, accounts you hold, your preferences and habits. Consider using two different browsers - one for confidential browsing (banking, business, etc.) and one for miscellaneous browsing.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33461","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1122","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33662","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_286","Image_287","si33359","si33374","si33385","si33495","si33513","si33535","si33553","si33565","si33577","si33589","si33601","si33613","si33625","si33637","si33649","si33461"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33662"},"question":{"interactionId":"33333","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  Another way for criminals to find your personal information (personal data, preferences, etc.) is from extracting it from your browser.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_288","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_289","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_289","roles":{}},{"id":"si33818","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1137","roles":{}},{"id":"si33715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_966","title":"6. ‘Jailbreaking’ or ‘Rooting’ your mobile device modifies it to allow free access  to its file system. This permits you to customize your device and download unauthorized apps and content. What is the down side of doing this?  Click all that apply:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1125","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33730","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1126","title":"It increases vulnerability to malicious apps and introduces potential stability problems ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33730","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34007q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si33726_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It increases vulnerability to malicious apps and introduces potential stability problems\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33737","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1127","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33741","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1128","title":"It violates security recommendations and end-user license agreements ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33741","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34007q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si33737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Assign a separate network from the one used for confidential information (banking) \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1129","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33752","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1130","title":"Malware can gain root access and acquire all data and information on the device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33752","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34007q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si33748_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Malware can gain root access and acquire all data and information on the device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33759","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1131","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1132","title":"Intruders can obtain your certificates, private keys, and purchasing receipts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33763","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34007q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si33759_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intruders can obtain your certificates, private keys, and purchasing receipts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Stolen account information can lead to unauthorized purchases and lock your device for ransom ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34736","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34007q5"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34732_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Stolen account information can lead to unauthorized purchases and lock your device\rfor ransom\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1136","roles":{}},{"id":"si33840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_219","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_220","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33880","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_221","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33898","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_222","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33922","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33946","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33994","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34007q5","for":"Slide34007q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33782","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1133","title":"Correct - Answers:   A,B,C,D,E  Bypassing the default security features on your device is not just a violation of security recommendations but is never a good idea. You may lose not just your data and confidential information but important functions and apps you need.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1134","title":"Incorrect - Answers: A,B,C,D,E  Bypassing the default security features on your device is not just a violation of security recommendations but is never a good idea. You may lose not just your data and confidential information but important functions and apps you need.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33806","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1135","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34007","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_288","Image_289","si33715","si33730","si33741","si33752","si33763","si34736","si33840","si33858","si33880","si33898","si33910","si33922","si33934","si33946","si33958","si33970","si33982","si33994","si33806"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34007"},"question":{"interactionId":"33689","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6. ‘Jailbreaking’ or ‘Rooting’ your mobile device modifies it to allow free access \rto its file system. This permits you to customize your device and download unauthorized apps and content. What is the down side of doing this? \rClick all that apply:\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","D","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_290","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_291","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_291","roles":{}},{"id":"si34133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1146","roles":{}},{"id":"si34052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_967","title":"7. You have done the responsible thing and backed up your personal data for the week on your external hard drive, what is the very next thing you should do?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1138","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1139","title":"Arrange a schedule of when to regularly back-up your data ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_538","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Arrange a schedule of when to regularly back-up your data\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1140","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1141","title":"Disconnect your hard drive  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_539","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Disconnect your hard drive \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si34747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34751","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Make a copy of the backed-up information in case you are hit with ransomware ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34747_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Make a copy of the backed-up information in case you are hit with ransomware\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34762","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34766","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Turn off your computer and disconnect the Wi-Fi so you cannot be infected overnight ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34762_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Turn off your computer and disconnect the Wi-Fi so you cannot be infected overnight\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34777","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34781","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34777_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1145","roles":{}},{"id":"si34155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_223","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_224","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_225","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_226","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34225","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34249","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34261","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34273","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34285","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34297","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34322q6","for":"Slide34322q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34097","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1142","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Once you have copied all of your information to your hard drive, it will only be safe if you disconnect it from your device and Wi-Fi. Leaving it connected is just as if you saved the information on your connected computer and could still be open to hacking or ransom.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1143","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Once you have copied all of your information to your hard drive, it will only be safe if you disconnect it from your device and Wi-Fi. Leaving it connected is just as if you saved the information on your connected computer and could still be open to hacking or ransom.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1144","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34322","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_290","Image_291","si34052","si34067","si34078","si34751","si34766","si34781","si34155","si34173","si34195","si34213","si34225","si34237","si34249","si34261","si34273","si34285","si34297","si34309","si34121"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34322"},"question":{"interactionId":"34026","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. You have done the responsible thing and backed up your personal data for the week on your external hard drive, what is the very next thing you should do?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_292","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_292","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_293","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_293","roles":{}},{"id":"si34493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1161","roles":{}},{"id":"si34379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_968","title":"8. You are leaving the office to work from home. You have your computer with you but need to stop at the store, best practice involves (check all that apply):  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1147","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1148","title":"Taking your computer and keeping it with you in the store  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34394","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34682q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Taking your computer and keeping it with you in the store \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1149","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1150","title":"Ensuring your computer is locked safely in the trunk of the car ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34405","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34682q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensuring your computer is locked safely in the trunk of the car\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34412","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1151","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1152","title":"Asking someone in the store to keep their eye on it for you while you shop ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34416","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34682q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34412_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Asking someone in the store to keep their eye on it for you while you shop\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34423","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1153","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1154","title":"Taking it home (shop another time) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34427","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34682q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34423_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Taking it home (shop another time)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34434","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1155","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1156","title":"Ensuring the car doors are locked, the computer is protected by your password. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34438","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide34682q7"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si34434_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensuring the car doors are locked, the computer is protected by your password.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si34487","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1160","roles":{}},{"id":"si34515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_227","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34533","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_228","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34555","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_229","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34573","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_230","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34633","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide34682q7","for":"Slide34682q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34457","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1157","title":"Correct - Answer:  A,D  Many computers are stolen from locked vehicles and locked trunks. When travelling with your device, you should always keep it with you. When just walking away, ensure it is secured. Your computer, like your phone, has confidential information, you wouldn’t leave it alone and exposed.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34469","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1158","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A,D  Many computers are stolen from locked vehicles and locked trunks. When travelling with your device, you should always keep it with you. When just walking away, ensure it is secured. Your computer, like your phone, has confidential information, you wouldn’t leave it alone and exposed.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si34481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1159","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide34682","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_292","Image_293","si34379","si34394","si34405","si34416","si34427","si34438","si34515","si34533","si34555","si34573","si34585","si34597","si34609","si34621","si34633","si34645","si34657","si34669","si34481"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide34682"},"question":{"interactionId":"34353","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. You are leaving the office to work from home. You have your computer with you but need to stop at the store, best practice involves (check all that apply):\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_239","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_269","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_269","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_273","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_273","roles":{}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_271","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"  Stay Current With   Information Security   By Subscribing to the    Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_271","Button_4","si19054","si19068","Text_Caption_5","SmartShape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":6000},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Jul2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"Jul2020Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide33272","Slide32237","Slide32582","Slide32927","Slide33662","Slide34007","Slide34322","Slide34682","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide33272q0","Slide32237q1","Slide32582q2","Slide32927q3","Slide33662q4","Slide34007q5","Slide34322q6","Slide34682q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide33272","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide32237","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide32582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide32927","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide33662","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide34007","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide34322","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide34682","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}